cyberseo.net 2018-10-19

# Privacy Policy – CyberSEO

CyberSEO.net takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

### General

CyberSEO.net tracks basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for administration and maintenance purposes only. CyberSEO.net does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer any personal information you provide.

### Cookies and Privacy

Cookies are small pieces of text data sent from our web server to the user’s hard drive that identify those who have previously visited our website. Controlling your privacy note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. You can configure your browser to reject cookies, however please note that this may cause some functionalities of our website to not work correctly.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to CyberSEO.net choose to interact with CyberSEO.net in ways that require CyberSEO.net to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that CyberSEO.net gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who use our support forums to provide a username and email address. In each case, CyberSEO.net collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with CyberSEO.net. CyberSEO.net does not disclose personally-identifying information. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Payment Processor Privacy Policy

Please see the 2Checkout.com (2CO) payment processor [Privacy Policy](https://www.2checkout.com/documentation/privacy.html "2Checkout.com \(2CO\) Privacy Policy") concerning additional collected information.
